scholarschoice.ca 2013-07-01

# Privacy Policy | Scholar's Choice - Teacher Store

Scholar's Choice is dedicated to protecting your privacy. We ensure that any personal information we obtain is kept confidential.

## What is Personal Information?

Personal information means _any information about an identifiable individual_. This includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, birth date, purchase information or e-mail address. As a Scholar's Choice customer, you provide us with this information in a variety of ways, such as joining our Scholasaurus Club membership program, entering in-store contests, signing up for our gift registry program, processing a return and calling for delivery or warranty information. In every case, Scholar's Choice adheres to strict guidelines when dealing with your personal information.

## Collecting Your Personal Information

When you provide Scholar's Choice with personal information, we inform you as to why we are collecting it. Scholar's Choice obtains your consent for the collection of your personal information. In some instances, where the purpose for collection is obvious, your consent is implied.

## Consent

We will collect, use or disclose your personal information only with your knowledge and consent, except where required or permitted by law. Scholar's Choice will not make your consent a requirement for the supply of a product or service other than as necessary to be able to supply the product or service.

Consent can be express or, in some circumstances, implied, and can be given in writing, by using or not using a check box, electronically, orally (in person or by telephone) or by your conduct, such as use of a product or service.

In determining the type of consent to obtain, Scholar's Choice will consider all relevant factors, including the sensitivity of the information and your reasonable expectations. You may withdraw your consent at any time, on reasonable notice, subject to legal or contractual restrictions.

## Commitment To Privacy

As a valued Scholar's Choice customer, any personal information that you give is maintained for the sole use of Scholar's Choice. Scholar's Choice will **not** divulge or use this information in any way other than for order processing and direct mail/e-mail/telephone communication from Scholar's Choice to you as our customer. We do **not** share or sell data.

## What We Gather and How We Use It

With your permission, we collect customer information including your name, school or business name, address, phone number, e-mail address and payment information (credit card number) so we can process an order or receive your entry into a contest. If we have any questions about your order or if you are a winner of a contest, we may contact you by e-mail or by phone.

As a valued Scholar's Choice customer, we will periodically send you e-mails and/or mailings to inform you of specials or promotions that we feel you may be interested in.

If at any time you decide you would no longer like to receive e-mails or mailings, you may contact us in writing and we will ease these correspondences.

           |       
---|---  
           | Scholar's Choice  
           | 2323 Trafalgar Street  
           | PO Box 7214  
           | London, ON, Canada  
           | N5Y 5S7  
           |    
  
You can also reach us at 1-800-265-1095 or [web@scholarschoice.ca](mailto:web@scholarschoice.ca) and request to have yourself removed from our marketing campaigns.

## Online Ordering

Your password is there to ensure no one else has access to your account. If you forget your password, just fill in the e-mail address you previously provided to us and a reminder will be sent to that address. Please protect your personal information by keeping your password secret, make sure you log off properly and take any necessary steps while using a shared computer.

Please note that credit card information is stored in an encrypted form; for your protection we use **Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption**.

## How We Use Web Technology

Like many websites, we use technology, such as cookies, that allow us to make your visit to our website easier by recognizing you when you return and help provide you with a customized experience.

## Customer Service Calls

When you call one of our Customer Service Representatives about a product, delivery, an installation, billing question or for customer service, you may be asked for information that identifies you along with additional information we need to help us promptly answer your question, such as your name and address and a phone number where we might contact you. We may retain this information to assist you in the future.
